A Guide to the Episcopal Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1905-1990
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Council--Committee on Parochial Reports (226); Council--Committee on State of the Church (226B) 1926 (Box-folder 16-57)
- Box 17 1926-30
- Council--general (227) 1926 (Box-folder 17-1)
- Council--lay delegates (228) 1926 (Box-folder 17-2)
- Council--Laymen's Night (229) 1926 (Box-folder 17-3)
- Council--Program (231) 1926 (Box-folder 17-4)
- Council--secretary's attention (232); Daughters of the King (233) 1926 (Box-folder 17-5)
- Council--Sunday papers (232) 1926 (Box-folder 17-6)
- Deaf Mutes (235) 1926 (Box-folder 17-7)
- Department--Field Diocesan (236) 1926 (Box-folder 17-8)
- Field Department--pledges for 1926 (236A) 1926 (Box-folder 17-9)
- Department of Finance--Diocesan (237) 1926 (Box-folder 17-10)
- Department of Publicity--Diocesan (238) 1926 (Box-folder 17-11)
- Department of Religious Education--Diocesan (239) 1926 (Box-folder 17-12)
- Department of Social Service--Diocesan (240); Depositions (241) 1926 (Box-folder 17-13)
- Diocesan Records (242) 1926 (Box-folder 17-14)
- Diocesan Offices--furniture, supplies, etc. (243); Diocesan Statistics (244) 1926 (Box-folder 17-15)
- Domestic and Foreign Missionary Society, New York (245); Dubose Memorial Church Training School (246) 1926 (Box-folder 17-16)
- Episcopal High School, Alexandria (248) 1926 (Box-folder 17-17)
- Episcopal Residence (249) 1926 (Box-folder 17-18)
- #250 1926 (Box-folder 17-19)
- Executive Board (251) 1926 (Box-folder 17-20)
- Federal Council of Church of Christ in America (253) 1926 (Box-folder 17-21)
- First National Exchange Bank--Roanoke (254) 1926 (Box-folder 17-22)
- Parish Houses and Chapels (1926: 296A) 1926 (Box-folder 17-23)
- Reverend R.A. Brayshaw 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-24)
- Reverend S.S. Hardy 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-25)
- Notes--cancelled, etc., and copies of new notes 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-26)
- Correspondence with Mr. A. Brooke Taylor 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-27)
- St. Paul RFD--Grace House and Mr. Tyler's correspondence 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-28)
- Reverend Roderick H. Jackson (215) 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-29)
- Reverend W.M. Purce (215) 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-30)
- Journal--mailing list (270) 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-31)
- Railways (1926-27: 302) 1926-27 (Box-folder 17-32)
- Edward W. Mellichampe (215) 1926-28 (Box-folder 17-33)
- Reverend G. Wallace Ribble (215) 1926-28 (Box-folder 17-34)
- Reverend John Ridout 1926-29 (Box-folder 17-35)
- C. Stanley Long (148, 215, 242) 1926-30 (Box-folder 17-36)
- Reverend C.S. Penniman (148, 215) 1926-30 (Box-folder 17-37)
- Accountant's Report 1927 (Box-folder 17-38)
- Diocesan Council 1927 (Box-folder 17-39)
- Report upon the parish lines of the parishes in the Diocese of Virginia, originally compiled by Reverend E.L. Goodwin, D.D., in 1905 1927 (Box-folder 17-40)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas 1927 (Box-folder 17-41)
- Abingdon--Good Shepherd (2); Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1927 (Box-folder 17-42)
- Amherst--Ascension (5); Amherst--Christ Mission (6); Appalachia--Grace (7) 1927 (Box-folder 17-43)
- Arrington--Trinity (8); Basic--St. Mary's (9) 1927 (Box-folder 17-44)
- Bedford--St. John's (10); Bedford--St. Philip's (11); Bent Mountain (12) 1927 (Box-folder 17-45)
- Bedford--St. Philip's--correspondence relative to rectory, tenant, etc. (12) 1927 (Box-folder 17-46)
- Big Island--St. Thomas (13); Big Stone Gap--Christ (14) 1927 (Box-folder 17-47)
- Blacksburg--Christ (15); Bluefield--St. Mary's (16) 1927 (Box-folder 17-48)
- Boonesboro--Trinity (17); Bristol--Emmanuel (18); Brookneal (19); Buchanan--Grace (20) 1927 (Box-folder 17-49)
- Buchanan--Trinity (21); Buena Vista--Christ (22); Byllesby (23) 1927 (Box-folder 17-50)
- Box 18 1927
- Callaway--St. Peter's (24); Christiansburg--St. Thomas' (26) 1927 (Box-folder 18-1)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (27); Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (28) 1927 (Box-folder 18-2)
- Covington--Emmanuel (31) 1927 (Box-folder 18-3)
- Covington--Grace Mission (32); Damascus--St. Paul's (33); Dante--St. Mark's (34) 1927 (Box-folder 18-4)
- Dungannon (36); Endicott--St. John's (39); Evington--Good Shepherd (40) 1927 (Box-folder 18-5)
- Evington--Our Savior (41); Fincastle--St. Mark's (42); Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (43); Forest-- Ivy Chapel (44); Forest--St. Stephen's (45) 1927 (Box-folder 18-6)
- Glade Spring--Grace (46); Gladys--Christ (47); Glasgow--St. John's (49); Honaker--Flat Rock (50); Hot Springs--St. Luke's (51) 1927 (Box-folder 18-7)
- Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (52); Ivanhoe--St. Barnabas (53); Keokee--St. Andrew's (54); Lebanon-- Mission (55) 1927 (Box-folder 18-8)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (56); Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (59) 1927 (Box-folder 18-9)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (60); Lynchburg--St. John's (62) 1927 (Box-folder 18-10)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (63); Madison Heights--Emmanuel (64) 1927 (Box-folder 18-11)
- Marion--Christ (65); Martinsville--Christ (66) 1927 (Box-folder 18-12)
- Massies Mill--Grace (67); Merrimac Mines--High Top (68); Montvale--St. Mark's (69); Narrows (69A) 1927 (Box-folder 18-13)
- Natural Bridge Station--Trinity (70); Nora--St. Stephen's (71); Norton--All Saints' (72) 1927 (Box-folder 18-14)
- Norwood--Christ (73); Pearisburg--Christ (74); Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (75) 1927 (Box-folder 18-15)
- Pounding Mill--Mission (77); Pulaski--Christ (78); Radford--Grace (79) 1927 (Box-folder 18-16)
- Richlands--Trinity (80) 1927 (Box-folder 18-17)
- Roanoke--Christ (81); Roanoke--St. John's (82) 1927 (Box-folder 18-18)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (83) 1927 (Box-folder 18-19)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (84); Rustburg--Trinity (85); St. Paul--Grace House (86); Salem--St. Paul's (88) 1927 (Box-folder 18-20)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (90); Schuyler--Christ (92); Six Mile Bridge (93); Staunton--Trinity (97) 1927 (Box-folder 18-21)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (96); Stratton (98) 1927 (Box-folder 18-22)
- Sweet Briar (99); Tazewell (101); Toms Creek (102) 1927 (Box-folder 18-23)
- Verona (103); Waynesboro--St. John's (105) 1927 (Box-folder 18-24)
- Wilder (107); Wytheville--St. John's (109); Wytheville--St. John's Chapel (110) 1927 (Box-folder 18-25)
- Yards (111); Miscellaneous A (175); Miscellaneous B (176) 1927 (Box-folder 18-26)
- Miscellaneous C (177); Miscellaneous D (178); Miscellaneous E (179) 1927 (Box-folder 18-27)
- Miscellaneous F (180); Miscellaneous G (181); Miscellaneous H (182); Miscellaneous I (183) 1927 (Box-folder 18-28)
- Miscellaneous J (184); Miscellaneous K (185); Miscellaneous L (186); Miscellaneous M (187); Miscellaneous N (188) 1927 (Box-folder 18-29)
- Miscellaneous O (189); Miscellaneous P (190) 1927 (Box-folder 18-30)
- Miscellaneous Q-R (191) 1927 (Box-folder 18-31)
- Miscellaneous S (192) 1927 (Box-folder 18-32)
- Miscellaneous T (193); Miscellaneous V (195) 1927 (Box-folder 18-33)
- Miscellaneous W (196) 1927 (Box-folder 18-34)
- Miscellaneous Y (198); Miscellaneous Z (199) 1927 (Box-folder 18-35)
- Box 19 1927
- Advance Work (200); Ambler, J.J. (201) 1927 (Box-folder 19-1)
- American Church Building Fund (202); American Church Institute for Negroes (202A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-2)
- Associate Missions (204) 1927 (Box-folder 19-3)
- Associate Missions--Special Committee (204A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-4)
- Baxter (206); Bishop's Discretionary Fund (207) 1927 (Box-folder 19-5)
- Bishop Payne Divinity School (208); Board of Church Finance (209) 1927 (Box-folder 19-6)
- Boy's Home (210) 1927 (Box-folder 19-7)
- Church Pension Fund (213) 1927 (Box-folder 19-8)
- Clergy Lists (214A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-9)
- Inquiries for ministry positions (B; C; D; F; G, 215) 1927 (Box-folder 19-10)
- Inquiries for ministry positions (H; J; M, 215) 1927 (Box-folder 19-11)
- Inquiries for ministry positions (M; O; P 215) 1927 (Box-folder 19-12)
- Reverend Richard H. Baker (215) 1927 (Box-folder 19-13)
- J.R. McAllister (215) 1927 (Box-folder 19-14)
- Clergy Rate Permits (216) 1927 (Box-folder 19-15)
- Evangelism--National and Diocesan Committee--Bishop's Crusade (217A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-16)
- Communion wine and wafers (218) 1927 (Box-folder 19-17)
- Conference of Diocesan Executive Secretaries (218A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-18)
- Convocation--James River (220); Convocation--New River (221) 1927 (Box-folder 19-19)
- Council--Bishop's address (221A); Council--1927 minutes (221B) 1927 (Box-folder 19-20)
- Council--Appendices (221C) 1927 (Box-folder 19-21)
- Council--Sundry papers (221D); Council--Architecture and Construction (222A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-22)
- Council--Church Intelligence (222B) 1927 (Box-folder 19-23)
- Council--Clerical support (224) 1927 (Box-folder 19-24)
- Council--Constitution and Canons (225) 1927 (Box-folder 19-25)
- National Council--Speakers' Bureau (225) 1927 (Box-folder 19-26)
- Council--Increase of ministry (225B); Dormant and Declining Parishes (225C) 1927 (Box-folder 19-27)
- Council--State of the Church (226B); Council--general (227) 1927 (Box-folder 19-28)
- Council--lay delegates (228) 1927 (Box-folder 19-29)
- Council--layman's night (229); Council--missionary night (230) 1927 (Box-folder 19-30)
- Council--program (231) 1927 (Box-folder 19-31)
- Council--secretary (232); Daughters of the King (233) 1927 (Box-folder 19-32)
- Deaf Mutes (235) 1927 (Box-folder 19-33)
- #236 1927 (Box-folder 19-34)
- Diocesan Field Department (236) 1927 (Box-folder 19-35)
- Field Department--pledges for 1927 (236B) 1927 (Box-folder 19-36)
- Diocesan Department of Finance (1927: 237) 1927 (Box-folder 19-37)
- Diocesan Department of Publilcity (238) 1927 (Box-folder 19-38)
- Diocesan Department of Religious Education (239) 1927 (Box-folder 19-39)
- Diocesan Department of Social Service (240); Deposition (241) 1927 (Box-folder 19-40)
- Diocesan Records (242) 1927 (Box-folder 19-41)
- Diocese Mission School (242A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-42)
- Diocesan Office (243) 1927 (Box-folder 19-43)
- Domestic and Foreign Missionary Society (245); Dormant and Declining Parishes (245A) 1927 (Box-folder 19-44)
- Dubose (246); Episcopal High School (248) 1927 (Box-folder 19-45)
- Episcopal Residence (249); Examining Chaplain (250) 1927 (Box-folder 19-46)
- Box 20 1927
- Executive Board--permanent (251) 1927 (Box-folder 20-1)
- Federal Council of Churches (253) 1927 (Box-folder 20-2)
- First National Exchange Bank (254) 1927 (Box-folder 20-3)
- General Convention (255); General Convention-- Apportion Committee (255A) 1927 (Box-folder 20-4)
- General Convention--simplified prayer book (255B); Girls Friendly (257) 1927 (Box-folder 20-5)
- Goldsmith (258) 1927 (Box-folder 20-6)
- Dr. Green (258 1/2) 1927 (Box-folder 20-7)
- George Lunn (259) 1927 (Box-folder 20-8)
- House of Bishops (263); Insurance (264) 1927 (Box-folder 20-9)
- Jerusalem and East Mission (265); Bishop Jett-- personal (267) 1927 (Box-folder 20-10)
- Journal--Publisher (271); Lawrenceville--St. Paul's School (274) 1927 (Box-folder 20-11)
- Lay Readers (275) 1927 (Box-folder 20-12)
- Laymen's League (276) 1927 (Box-folder 20-13)
- Lenten Mite Boxes (277) 1927 (Box-folder 20-14)
- Lenten Mite Box Offering--reports (277A) 1927 (Box-folder 20-15)
- Lenten Offering Celebration Attendance (277B); Letters Dimissory--given and received (279) 1927 (Box-folder 20-16)
- Living Church Annual (280); Library (281) 1927 (Box-folder 20-17)
- Mimeograph and Circular Letters (282) 1927 (Box-folder 20-18)
- Mosby Montague (283); National Council--Social Service (284) 1927 (Box-folder 20-19)
- National Council--Field Department (285) 1927 (Box-folder 20-20)
- National Council--Department of Missions (286) 1927 (Box-folder 20-21)
- National Council--Department of Publicity (287) 1927 (Box-folder 20-22)
- National Council--Religious Education (288) 1927 (Box-folder 20-23)
- National Council--foreign born division (288A); National Council--Lewis B. Franklin (289) 1927 (Box-folder 20-24)
- National Council--Woman's Auxiliary (291); Near East Relief (292) 1927 (Box-folder 20-25)
- #293 1927 (Box-folder 20-26)
- Notes (294); Order of Jamestown (294A) 1927 (Box-folder 20-27)
- Parochial Reports (297) 1927 (Box-folder 20-28)
- Presiding Bishop (299); Province of Washington (300) 1927 (Box-folder 20-29)
- Provincial Synod (Folder 1 of 2, 300A) 1927 (Box-folder 20-30)
- Provincial Synod (Folder 2 of 2, 300A) 1927 (Box-folder 20-31)
- Box 21 1927-28
- Provincial Synod--financing (300B) 1927 (Box-folder 21-1)
- Province of Washington--Synod 1927-credentials (300C) 1927 (Box-folder 21-2)
- Provincial Synod--women's organizations (300D) 1927 (Box-folder 21-3)
- Provincial Synod--Church School section (300E) 1927 (Box-folder 21-4)
- Provincial Synod--Registration and Hospitality Committees (300F) 1927 (Box-folder 21-5)
- Provincial Synod--exhibits (300G); Young People (301, 324) 1927 (Box-folder 21-6)
- Dr. E.R. Roger (303); Simplified Prayer Book (303A) 1927 (Box-folder 21-7)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (304) 1927 (Box-folder 21-8)
- Standing Committee (305) 1927 (Box-folder 21-9)
- Stuart Hall (306) 1927 (Box-folder 21-10)
- Sweet Briar College (307) 1927 (Box-folder 21-11)
- Theological Seminary--Virginia (309) 1927 (Box-folder 21-12)
- Treasurer of Diocese (310) 1927 (Box-folder 21-13)
- Trustees of the Diocese (311) 1927 (Box-folder 21-14)
- Vestries (314) 1927 (Box-folder 21-15)
- Virginia Episcopal School (315) 1927 (Box-folder 21-16)
- Episcopal Residence Committee (315) 1927 (Box-folder 21-17)
- St. Mary's Church, Basic (Waynesboro, Virginia, 317) 1927 (Box-folder 21-18)
- St. John's-in-the-mountains--fire insurance (317) 1927 (Box-folder 21-19)
- "January 1927 to December 1927, Inc." (317) 1927 (Box-folder 21-20)
- Visitations (317); Reverend John S. Wellford (318) 1927 (Box-folder 21-21)
- Women's Auxiliary--Diocesan (319) 1927 (Box-folder 21-22)
- Women Workers--prospective (Folder 1 of 2, 320) 1927 (Box-folder 21-23)
- Women Workers--prospective (Folder 2 of 2, 320) 1927 (Box-folder 21-24)
- World Conference on Faith and Order (321); Young (323) 1927 (Box-folder 21-25)
- Diocesan Mission School Foundation (325) 1927 (Box-folder 21-26)
- Reverend Morrison Bethea 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-27)
- Miscellaneous 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-28)
- Journal--mailing list (205) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-29)
- William A. Lillycrop (215) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-30)
- Reverend Rice (215) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-31)
- Executive Board--permanent (251) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-32)
- Bishop Jett--vacation (268) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-33)
- Bishop Jett--vacation (268); Council--appendices (268A); Journal--mailing list (270) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-34)
- Virginia Episcopal School (305) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-35)
- Virginia Summer School (316) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-36)
- Church and Rectory at Bedford, Virginia (317) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-37)
- Visitations (317) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-38)
- Council--minutes and papers (319) 1927-28 (Box-folder 21-39)
- Box 22 1927-30
- Reverend Reginald G. Davis 1927-29 (Box-folder 22-1)
- Portland Lots 1927-29 (Box-folder 22-2)
- Reverend Frank Cox (148, 215) 1927-29 (Box-folder 22-3)
- Reverend Robert A. Goodwin (148, 215) 1927-29 (Box-folder 22-4)
- Church Pension Fund (318) 1927-29 (Box-folder 22-5)
- William H. Laird (148, 215) 1927-30 (Box-folder 22-6)
- Douglas Matthews (148) 1927-30 (Box-folder 22-7)
- Reverend Paul L. Powles (148, 215) 1927-30 (Box-folder 22-8)
- Reverend Herbert S. Osborne (215) 1927-30 (Box-folder 22-9)
- Accountant's Report 1928 (Box-folder 22-10)
- Miscellaneous 1928 (Box-folder 22-11)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (1); Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1928 (Box-folder 22-12)
- Amherst--Ascension (5); Amherst--Christ Mission (6); Appalachia--Grace (7); Arrington--Trinity (8) 1928 (Box-folder 22-13)
- Basic--St. Mary's (9); Bedford--St. John's (10) 1928 (Box-folder 22-14)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (11); Big Island--St. Thomas' (13); Big Stone Gap--Christ (14); Blacksburg-- Christ (15) 1928 (Box-folder 22-15)
- Bedford--St. Philip's--correspondence relative to rectory, tenant, etc. (12) 1928 (Box-folder 22-16)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (16); Boonesboro--Trinity (17); Bristol--Emmanuel (18); Buchanan--Grace (20); Buchanan--Trinity (21) 1928 (Box-folder 22-17)
- Buena Vista--Christ (22); Byllesby (23) 1928 (Box-folder 22-18)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (24); Christiansburg--St. Thomas (26); Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (28) 1928 (Box-folder 22-19)
- Clinchco--Moss Mission (29); Coeburn (30); Covington--Emmanuel (31); Covington--Grace Mission (32) 1928 (Box-folder 22-20)
- Ferrum--St. John's-in-the-Mountains--history (30) 1928 (Box-folder 22-21)
- Damascus--St. Paul's (33); Dante--St. Mark's (34); Drill--Mission (35); Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (38) 1928 (Box-folder 22-22)
- Endicott--St. John's (39); Evington--Good Shepherd (40) 1928 (Box-folder 22-23)
- Evington--Our Savior (41); Fincastle--St. Mark's (42); Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (43); Forest-- Ivy Chapel (44) 1928 (Box-folder 22-24)
- Glade Spring--Grace (46); Gladys--Christ (47); Glasgow--St. John's (49) 1928 (Box-folder 22-25)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (51); Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (52); Ivanhoe--St. Barnabas (53) 1928 (Box-folder 22-26)
- Keokee--St. Andrew's (54); Lebanon--Mission (55); Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (56) 1928 (Box-folder 22-27)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (59) 1928 (Box-folder 22-28)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (60); Lynchburg--St. John's (62) 1928 (Box-folder 22-29)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (68); Madison Heights--Emmanuel (64); Marion--Christ (65) 1928 (Box-folder 22-30)
- Martinsville--Christ (66); Massies Mill--Grace (67); Montvale--St. Mark's (69); Natural Bridge-- Trinity (70) 1928 (Box-folder 22-31)
- Nora--Stephens (71); Norton--All Saints' (72); Norwood--Christ (73); Pearisburg--Christ (74) 1928 (Box-folder 22-32)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (75); Pocahontas--Christ (76); Pounding Mill--Mission (77) 1928 (Box-folder 22-33)
- Pulaski--Christ (78) 1928 (Box-folder 22-34)
- Radford--Grace (79); Roanoke--Christ (81); Roanoke--St. John's (82) 1928 (Box-folder 22-35)
- Richlands--Trinity (80) 1928 (Box-folder 22-36)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (83) 1928 (Box-folder 22-37)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (84); Rustburg--Trinity (85); St. Paul--Grace House (86); Sandy Ridge--St. Paul (87) 1928 (Box-folder 22-38)
- Salem--St. Paul's (88); Saltville--St. Paul's (90); Schuyler--Christ (92); Six Mile Bridge--Grace (93) 1928 (Box-folder 22-39)
- South Clinchfield (94); South Clinchfield--Bandmill (95); Splashdam (95A); Staunton--Emmanuel (96) 1928 (Box-folder 22-40)
- Staunton--Trinity (97); Stratton (98); Sweet Briar--College (99); Tazewell (101) 1928 (Box-folder 22-41)
- Tom's Creek (102); Verona (103); Warm Springs-- Christ (104); Waynesboro--St. John's (105) 1928 (Box-folder 22-42)
- Wilder (107); Wytheville--St. John's (109); Yards (111); Miscellaneous A (175) 1928 (Box-folder 22-43)
- Box 23 1928
- Reverend Francis A. Gray (148) 1928 (Box-folder 23-1)
- Inquiries for Ministry Positions (N; R, 148, 215) 1928 (Box-folder 23-2)
- Miscellaneous C (177); Miscellaneous D (178); Miscellaneous E (179) 1928 (Box-folder 23-3)
- Miscellaneous F (180); Miscellaneous G (181); Miscellaneous H (182); Miscellaneous I (183) 1928 (Box-folder 23-4)
- Miscellaneous J (184); Miscellaneous K (185); Miscellaneous B (176) 1928 (Box-folder 23-5)
- Miscellaneous L (186); Miscellaneous M (187) 1928 (Box-folder 23-6)
- Miscellaneous N (188); Miscellaneous O (189); Miscellaneous P (190) 1928 (Box-folder 23-7)
- Miscellaneous Q-R (191); Miscellaneous S (192); Miscellaneous T (193) 1928 (Box-folder 23-8)
- Miscellaneous V (195); Miscellaneous W (196) 1928 (Box-folder 23-9)
- Advance Work (200); Amber, J.J. (201); American Church Building Fund (202); American Institute for Negroes (202A) 1928 (Box-folder 23-10)
- Appeals (202A 1/2) 1928 (Box-folder 23-11)
- Architecture and Construction (202B); Associate Mission (204) 1928 (Box-folder 23-12)
- #205 1928 (Box-folder 23-13)
- Baxter, W.C (206); Bills Unpaid (206A) 1928 (Box-folder 23-14)
- Bishop's Address (206B) 1928 (Box-folder 23-15)
- Bishop's Discretionary Fund (207); Bishop Payne Divinity School (208); Board of Church Finance (209) 1928 (Box-folder 23-16)
- #209 1928 (Box-folder 23-17)
- Boys' Home--Covington (210) 1928 (Box-folder 23-17)
- Chancellor (211); A Church Intelligence (212A) 1928 (Box-folder 23-18)
- Church Pension Fund (213) 1928 (Box-folder 23-19)
- Clergy List and General (214A) 1928 (Box-folder 23-20)
- Reverend Morris W. Derr (215) 1928 (Box-folder 23-21)
- Inquiries for Ministry Positions (B; C; D; E; F; G; H; L; M, 215) 1928 (Box-folder 23-22)
- Clerical Support (Committee on, 216); Clippings (217); Communion wine and wafers (218) 1928 (Box-folder 23-23)
- Consents (219); Constitution and Canons (219A); Convocation (221) 1928 (Box-folder 23-24)
- Council--general (223) 1928 (Box-folder 23-25)
- Council--lay delegates (224) 1928 (Box-folder 23-26)
- Council--minutes (225); Council--Mission Night (226) 1928 (Box-folder 23-27)
- Council--program (227) 1928 (Box-folder 23-28)
- Council--Secretary (228); Crusade--Evangelism (228A); Daughters of the King (233) 1928 (Box-folder 23-29)
- Deaf Mutes (235); Diocesan Department--field (236) 1928 (Box-folder 23-30)
- Diocesan Department--field--1928 pledges (236B); Field Department--deficit (236C) 1928 (Box-folder 23-31)
- Diocesan Department--finance (237); Diocesan Department--publicity (238) 1928 (Box-folder 23-32)
- Box 24 1928
- Diocese of --- (242) 1928 (Box-folder 24-1)
- Diocesan Mission School (242A) 1928 (Box-folder 24-2)
- Diocesan Office (243) 1928 (Box-folder 24-3)
- Domestic and Foreign Missionary (245); Dubose (246); Episcopal High School (248) 1928 (Box-folder 24-4)
- Episcopal Residence (249); Examining Chaplains (250) 1928 (Box-folder 24-5)
- Federal Council of Churches (253); Financial Appeals (253 1/2); First National Exchange Bank (254) 1928 (Box-folder 24-6)
- General Convention (255) 1928 (Box-folder 24-7)
- General Convention--calling rectors (255A) 1928 (Box-folder 24-8)
- General Convention--delegation (255B); Girls Friendly (257); Gunn, George (259) 1928 (Box-folder 24-9)
- Women Workers (257) 1928 (Box-folder 24-10)
- Historiographers (261); House of Bishops (263); Insurance (264); Jerusalem and East Missions (265) 1928 (Box-folder 24-11)
- Bishop Jett--personal (267) 1928 (Box-folder 24-12)
- Journal Publisher (271); Lawrenceville--St. Paul's School (274); Lay Readers (275) 1928 (Box-folder 24-13)
- Laymen's League (276); Lenten Mite Box Offering (277) 1928 (Box-folder 24-14)
- Reports--Mite Box Offering (277A); Letters Dimissory--given and received (279) 1928 (Box-folder 24-15)
- #278 1928 (Box-folder 24-16)
- Living Church Annual (280); Library (281); Maps (281A) 1928 (Box-folder 24-17)
- Fred H. Miller (281B); Mimeograph and Circular letters (282); Robert Nance (283 1/2) 1928 (Box-folder 24-18)
- National Council--social service (284); National Council--Field Department (285) 1928 (Box-folder 24-19)
- National Council--Missions Department (286) 1928 (Box-folder 24-20)
- National Council Religious Education (288); National Council--foreign born (288A) 1928 (Box-folder 24-21)
- National Council--L.B. Franklin (289) 1928 (Box-folder 24-22)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (291); Near East Relief (292); News Notes (293) 1928 (Box-folder 24-23)
- Notes (294); Parish Definitions (296B); Parochial Reports (297) 1928 (Box-folder 24-24)
- Presiding Bishop (299); Province of Washington (300) 1928 (Box-folder 24-25)
- Railways (302) 1928 (Box-folder 24-26)
- Revisions of Prayer Book, Committee on (302A); Rogers, Dr. E.R. (303); Simplified Prayer Book (303A) 1928 (Box-folder 24-27)
- President's statements (303) 1928 (Box-folder 24-28)
- "Helps to Use the Book of Common Prayer" (303A) 1928 (Box-folder 24-29)
- Box 25 1928-32
- J.A. Scott (303X) 1928 (Box-folder 25-1)
- Boys' Home--Covington (304) 1928 (Box-folder 25-2)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (304) 1928 (Box-folder 25-3)
- Special Services and Prayers (304A) 1928 (Box-folder 25-4)
- Standing Committee (305); State of the Church--Committee on (305A) 1928 (Box-folder 25-5)